question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom "
                 "Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during "
                 "the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate "
                 "the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
]
